<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Computers And Stuff</title><subtitle>A minimal, responsive, and powerful Jekyll theme for presenting professional writing.</subtitle> <updated>2026-02-19T20:12:03+00:00</updated> <author> <name>Luke</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2026 Luke </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Thoughts and Resources on Self-Paced Computer Networking Education</title><link href="/posts/Alternative-Learning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thoughts and Resources on Self-Paced Computer Networking Education" /><published>2026-02-19T20:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2026-02-19T20:11:31+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/Alternative-Learning/</id> <content src="/posts/Alternative-Learning/" /> <author> <name>Luke</name> </author> <category term="school," /> <category term="networking" /> <summary> It has been a while since my last post. Life happens, school and work are busy, but I am back. Today, I wanted to compile a list of different resources that can help an independent learner with networking skills. Going through schooling for a networking &amp;amp; cybersecurity degree has shown me how much independent work can be done. I wanted to help those who are not able to attend a university, ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Channel Updates, A Receipt Printer, and The Future of Computers And Stuff</title><link href="/posts/Channel-Updates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Channel Updates, A Receipt Printer, and The Future of Computers And Stuff" /><published>2023-10-08T22:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2023-10-08T22:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/Channel-Updates/</id> <content src="/posts/Channel-Updates/" /> <author> <name>Luke</name> </author> <category term="updates" /> <summary> Hello! It has been a while. Two years since my last upload of an Apple Airport AP. To anyone who has been following, I’ve been pretty busy and I’m trying to find time for the channel. However, recently I ran into a roadblock. About a couple months ago I released a Roblox game that allows you to print asset images on a real life receipt thermal printer at a low price. The prints could be vie... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>NEC P120 Teardown - What makes up a 90s cell phone?</title><link href="/posts/NEC-P120-teardown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NEC P120 Teardown - What makes up a 90s cell phone?" /><published>2022-08-17T21:36:31+00:00</published> <updated>2022-08-18T03:16:55+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/NEC-P120-teardown/</id> <content src="/posts/NEC-P120-teardown/" /> <author> <name>Luke</name> </author> <category term="teardown" /> <summary> Phones have come a long way from being bricks with minimal functionality to devices in which the “phone” function is not the most used. This NEC P120 is a look at the past and how you could make phone calls away from home. Disassembly After removing the battery there are 4 weird screws you need to remove I don’t know what kind of screws these are, but I was able to remove them with tweez... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>The Brain of A Hotel - Hac... or Inspecting the Tech Inside Hotels</title><link href="/posts/hotel-tech-hacks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Brain of A Hotel - Hac... or Inspecting the Tech Inside Hotels" /><published>2022-07-07T21:36:31+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-07T21:42:57+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/hotel-tech-hacks/</id> <content src="/posts/hotel-tech-hacks/" /> <author> <name>Luke</name> </author> <category term="hacking" /> <summary> NOTE: The contents in this post are for educational purposes. Do not attempt any of the actions outlined here. You could get banned from hotels, fined, and make an IT guy’s job a lot harder. I recently stayed at a couple of hotels over the summer and as always I had to see what tech powered them. Both hotels were clean and I had a good stay except for the unexpected wakeup call. The first ho... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>New site! How it's going after moving to Jekyll and GitHub Pages</title><link href="/posts/new-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New site! How it's going after moving to Jekyll and GitHub Pages" /><published>2022-05-23T22:29:31+00:00</published> <updated>2022-05-23T22:29:31+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/new-blog/</id> <content src="/posts/new-blog/" /> <author> <name>Luke</name> </author> <category term="blog" /> <summary> If you’re reading this you probably noticed the change. No longer am I using blogspot/blogger to post my updates, I am now using Github pages and a static site generator called Jekyll. It’s been a bit of a bumpy start to learn how the software works, but that’s what happens with software. Trial and error will bring you closer to success (usually). After messing around with Jekyll’s settings, ... </summary> </entry> </feed>
